A Guide to the Papers of John Randolph of Roanoke, 1781-1860, [n.d.]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Letters and Documents
  - John Randolph to Henry Tucker, 1809 July 20, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed. #3579. (Box-folder 2:31)
    Taped to sheet with engraving and clipping pasted to it.
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1809 July 31, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:32)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1809 August 20, ALS, 5 pp. on 3 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:33)
  - J[udith] Randolph to John Randolph, 1809 August 22, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:34)
  - J[udith] Randolph to John Randolph, 1809 August 27, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:35)
    With note inscribed on address leaf to "Mr. Hay."
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1809 September 14, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:36)
  - J[udith] R[andolph] to John Randolph, Saturday Sunrise. [1809 October], ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:37)
  - James Mercer Garnett to John Randolph, 1809 October 3, ALS, 6 pp. on 4 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:38)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1809 October 22, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; #1883. (Box-folder 2:39)
  - J[udith] R[andolph] to [John Randolph], 1809 November 3, ALS, 1 p.; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 2:40)
  - J[udith] Randolph to John Randolph, 1809 November 3, ALS, 5 pp. on 2 l.; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 2:41)
  - St. George Tucker to John Randolph, 1809 November 7, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:42)
  - N.[athaniel] Beverley Tucker to [John Randolph], 1809 November 12, ALS, 4 pp. on 2 l.; #3400. (Box-folder 2:43)
    The last page appears to be in another hand.
  - M[ary] Tucker to John Randolph, 1809 November 28, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:44)
  - St. George Tucker to John Randolph, 1809 December 11, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #3400. (Box-folder 2:45)
    Note by Tucker on address leaf to the postmaster.
  - James Mercer Garnett to John Randolph, 1809 December 19, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:46)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, 1809 December 23, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #3400. (Box-folder 2:47)
    Missing portion of letter.
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1809 December 25, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:48)
  - James Mercer Garnett to John Randolph, 1810 January 9, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:49)
  - N.[athaniel] Beverley Tucker to [John Randolph], 1810 January 9, ALS, 5 pp. on 2 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:50)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 January 17, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:51)
  - John Randolph to Joseph Clay, 1810 January 18, ALS, 1 p.; with typescript. #8140. (Box-folder 2:52)
    Glued to backing.
  - James Mercer Garnett to John Randolph, 1810 January 23, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:53)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 January 29, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:54)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 February 12, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; postmark illegible. #1883. (Box-folder 2:55)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 February 27, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:56)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 March 13, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:57)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 March 20, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:58)
  - John Randolph to Joseph Clay, 1810 March 23, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l. Taped along folds; brittle paper. #8477. (Box-folder 2:59)
  - John Randolph to "my dear sister" [Anne Frances Bland (Tucker) Coalter], 1810 April 6, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 2:60)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 April 10, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:61)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 April 10, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:62)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 April 11, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:63)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1810 April 24, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:64)
  - Joseph Bryan to John Randolph, 1810 May 27, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; postmarked Savannah GA, May 28. #3400. (Box-folder 2:65)
  - John Randolph to Mrs. [Fulwar] Skipwith, 1810 June 6, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; postmarked Richmond VA, June 10. #2988. (Box-folder 2:66)
  - James Monroe to John Randolph, 1810 June 15., #3339. (Box-folder 2:67)
  - N.[athaniel] Beverley Tucker to [John Randolph], 1810 June 17, ALS, 1 p.; with address on verso; #3400. (Box-folder 2:68)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 June 29, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf, with wax seal; #1883. (Box-folder 2:69)
  - John Randolph to Mrs. Fulwar Skipwith, 1810 June 29, ALS, 1 pp.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; docketed. #6489. (Box-folder 2:70)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 July 9, ALS, 5 pp. on 3 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:71)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 July 31, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:72)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 July 31, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:73)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 August 14, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:74)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 August 14, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:75)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, 1810 August 19, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #3400. (Box-folder 2:76)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 September 28, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:77)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 October 10, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; postmarked Richmond VA October 16. #1883. (Box-folder 2:78)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 October 16, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:79)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 October 22, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:80)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 November 6, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:81)
    The first instance in this collection signed "John Randolph of Roanoke."
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1810 November 6, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:82)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, 1810 November 10, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #3400. (Box-folder 2:83)
    Note on address leaf stating that the letter can also "be opened by Mrs. Mary Tucker or Nathaniel B. Tucker" in Randolph's absence.
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1810 November 12, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:84)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 January 1, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:85)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 January 21, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:86)
  - John Randolph to J[oseph] H. Nicholson, 1811 January 28, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. #3440-a. (Box-folder 2:87)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 January 29, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:88)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 February 4, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:89)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 February 10, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; Partial note on verso of third page. #1883. (Box-folder 2:90)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 February 11, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:91)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 February 17, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:92)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 February 19, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:93)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 February 22, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:94)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 February 26, ALS, 5 pp. on 3 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:95)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 March 13, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:96)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 March 16, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:97)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 March 19, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:98)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 March 19, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:99)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 March 24, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:100)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 March 25, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:101)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 March 29, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:102)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, 1811 April 4, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #3400. (Box-folder 2:103)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 April 7, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached partial address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 2:104)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 April 9, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:105)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 April 11, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:106)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 April 15, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:107)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 April 16, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:108)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 April 20, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:109)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 April 24, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:110)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 April 30, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:111)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 May 5, ALS, 5 pp. on 3 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:112)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, 1811 May 11, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 2:113)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 May 21, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 2:114)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 May 27, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf (Box-folder 2:115)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 June 15, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:116)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 June 22, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 2:117)
  - John Randolph to [Anne Frances Bland (Tucker)] Coalter, 1811 June 23, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 3:1)
  - [John Randolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 June 24, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:2)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 July 7, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Joseph Bryan to John Randolph, 1811 July 14, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l. #3400. (Box-folder 3:4)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 July 23, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:5)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 July [25], ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 August [5], ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - [John Randolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 August 7, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 August 12, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:9)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [Anne] Frances Bland [(Tucker)] Coalter, 1811 August 19, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; partial docket. #2113. (Box-folder 3:10)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 August 20, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:11)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 August 25, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Fanny Bland Coalter to John Randolph, [1811 August 30], ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #3400. (Box-folder 3:13)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [Anne] Frances Bland [(Tucker)] Coalter, 1811 September 9, ALS, 1 p.; with address on verso; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 3:14)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 September 9, ALS, 1 p.; with address on verso; #1883. (Box-folder 3:15)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1811 September 15, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:16)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1811 September 17, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:17)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 September 22, ALS, 3 p. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 3:18)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 October 7, ALS, 3 p. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; #1883. (Box-folder 3:19)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1811 October 30, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; postmarked Richmond VA, November 2. #1883. (Box-folder 3:20)
  - J[ohn] Randolph to Judith Randolph, 1811 November 17, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with address leaf; docketed; postmarked Georgetown, November 20. #3400. (Box-folder 3:21)
  - James Monroe to John Randolph, 1811 November-., #5842. (Box-folder 3:22)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1811 December 13, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:23)
  - [John Randolph] to [Mr. Ingraham], 1811 December 21, AL, 1 p. #9511-m. (Box-folder 3:24)
  - John Randolph to Mrs. Brockenbrough, 1811 December 31, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; 19th century copy? in unidentified hand. #8264. (Box-folder 3:25)
    Letter of condolence to Mrs. Brockenbrough following Richmond Theatre fire.
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 January 8, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:26)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 January 12, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:27)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 January 20, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:28)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 February 1, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:29)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 February 5, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:30)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 February 11, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:31)
  - John Randolph to Judith Randolph, 1812 February 12, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; docketed; postmarked Georgetown, February 12. #3400. (Box-folder 3:32)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 February 13, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:33)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 February 18, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:34)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 February 18, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:35)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 February 22, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:36)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 February 25, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:37)
  - Joseph Bryan to John Randolph, 1812 March 1, ALS, 5 pp. on 2 l.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; docketed; postmarked Savannah GA, March 3. #3400. (Box-folder 3:38)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 March 8, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:39)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 March 10, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:40)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 March 13, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:41)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 March 24, ALS, 6 pp. on 3 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:42)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 March 30, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:43)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 March 31, ANS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:44)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 April 2, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:45)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 April 7, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:46)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 April 7, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:47)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 April 9, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:48)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 April 12, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:49)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 April 14, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:50)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 April 16, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:51)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 April 21, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:52)
  - Joseph Bryan to John Randolph, 1812 April 23, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed; postmarked Savannah GA, April 2[3]? #3400. (Box-folder 3:53)
  - John Brockenbrough to John Randolph, [1812 April 26], ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; docketed postmarked Richmond VA, April 26. #3339. (Box-folder 3:54)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 April 28, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:55)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 April 29, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:56)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 May 26, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:57)
  - John Randolph to Mrs. Nicholson, 1812 May 27, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf. #3579. (Box-folder 3:58)
    Note on address leaf: "Given by Mrs. Nicholson"
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 June 2, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:59)
  - [John Randolph] to [Mr. Oliver], 1812 June 5, AL, 1 p. #7083. (Box-folder 3:60)
  - John Randolph to Micajah Woods, 1812 June 5, AL, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with address leaf; postmarked Georgetown, June 6. #38-404. (Box-folder 3:61)
    Includes a note by Mr. Woods about Randolph's missing signature.
  - John Randolph to David Parish, 1812 June 13, ALS, 1 p.; docketed. #4319-a. (Box-folder 3:62)
  - John Randolph to David Parish, 1812 June 18, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed. #4319-a. (Box-folder 3:63)
  - John Randolph to David Parish, 1812 June 18, ALS, 1 p. Letter mounted to a sheet with an engraving of Randolph. #3579. (Box-folder 3:64)
  - John Randolph to David Parish, 1812 June 23, ALS, 1 p.; docketed. #4319-b. (Box-folder 3:65)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 June 30, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:66)
  - Printed article by John Randolph, 1812 July 2, D. 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:67)
  - [John Randolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 July 7, AL, addressed by John Randolph, 1 p.; with address on verso; postmarked Georgetown, July 7; #1883. (Box-folder 3:68)
    Presumably refers to and originally enclosed the Printed Document from 1812 July 2.
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 July 14, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:69)
  - John Randolph to "My dear sister," 1812 July 17, ALS, 1 p.; #2118. (Box-folder 3:70)
    Mentions Mr. Mercer of Fredericksburg.
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 July 20, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:71)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 July 24, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:72)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 August 2, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; includes transcript by John Randolph of letter by Peter Brown, dated Raleigh, 1812 July 15; #1883. (Box-folder 3:73)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 August 9, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:74)
  - James M[ercer] Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 August 11, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:75)
  - John Randolph to H[armanus] Bleecker, 1812 August 16, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with separate address leaf, with partial wax seal; docketed. In bound volume (Box 8), page 4; followed by typed transcript. The transcript incorrectly states that the letter was written on the 10th rather than the 16th. Address leaf out of sequence. #3677. (Box-folder 3:76)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 August 16, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:77)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 August 18, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:78)
  - John Randolph to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 August 21, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf; Includes transcript by John Randolph of a Peter Browne letter dated Raleigh, July 15, 1812, continuing the transcription further than his earlier 1812 August 2 transcription to Garnett. #1883. (Box-folder 3:79)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer Garnett], 1812 August 31, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:80)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 September 13, ALS, 4 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:81)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 September 14, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:82)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 October 1, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:83)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 October 14, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:84)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to H[armanus] Bleecker, 1812 November 7, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf; docketed; postmarked Richmond VA, November 7. In bound volume (Box 8), page 6; includes typed transcription. #3677. (Box-folder 3:85)
  - John St. George Randolph to John Randolph, 1812 November 8, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf, with wax seal; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 3:86)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 November 17, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:87)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 November 17, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:88)
  - John St. George Randolph to John Randolph, 1812 November 18, ALS, 1 p.; with attached address leaf, with wax seal; docketed. #3400. (Box-folder 3:89)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 November 24, ALS, 1 p.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:90)
  - John Randolph to Charles Harris, 1812 November 27, ALS, 1 p.; photostat. #4346. (Box-folder 3:91)
  - John Randolph to [James Mercer] Garnett, 1812 November 30, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:92)
  - James Mercer Garnett to [John Randolph], 1812 December 1, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:93)
  - James Mercer Garnett to John Randolph, 1812 December 5, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l.; with attached address leaf, with partial wax seal; docketed; #1883. (Box-folder 3:94)
  - J[ohn] R[andolph] to James Mercer Garnett, 1812 December 7, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l.; #1883. (Box-folder 3:95)
  - John Randolph to Elizabeth Tucker Coalter and Betty Tucker Coalter, 1812 December 10--1824 April 25, ALSs, 68 pp. on 68 l.; copies in unidentified hand. #3400. (Box-folder 3:96)